adsovo.com 2011-11-29

# Privacy Policy « ADSOVO

## ADSOVO Inc. Privacy Policy

ADSOVO Inc., a Washington State corporation, and its global subsidiaries and affiliates (“ADSOVO”) is committed to protecting the privacy of all Internet users, Websites, Publishers and Advertisers. This Privacy Policy statement explains how ADSOVO operates to protect your privacy.

Please note that ADSOVO may find it necessary, or be legally obligated, to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected prior to the effective date of the policy change. ADSOVO reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time without notice by posting of such modification herein. Members (as defined below) and visitors should review this Privacy Policy periodically to note any changes that may have occurred. A Member is a corporation, other legal entity, or adult person that has applied to ADSOVO in accordance with the terms, conditions and procedures outlined in this Website.

ADSOVO does not collect any personal information about visitors to, or users of, this Website solely as a result of such visits or usage, other than persons or entities joining ADSOVO’s Network as a Member pursuant to either a written or online contract.

When an Internet user clicks on one of ADSOVO’s served advertisements (running throughout the Network), ADSOVO does collect ad delivery and reporting (type of browser, operating system, IP address, domain type, page(s) visited, date and time of when an Internet user has responded to an advertisement, etc.). None of the data can be linked to any individual Internet user, and therefore it cannot be used for personal identification or profiling.

ADSOVO does not collect any personally identifiable information regarding the user that clicked on the ad (e.g. name, address, social security number, e-mail address, etc.), however, upon clicking on an ADSOVO served advertisement, users may be directed to 3rd-party forms where such data may be requested by the 3rd-party and user may voluntarily opt to provide such information, at the sole discretion of the user and with no knowledge of ADSOVO.

Some information is collected through Cookies as described below.

### Cookies

An Internet user’s browser normally places Cookies that contain small amounts of data on the Internet user’s computer after a visit to any Website. Cookies assist ADSOVO in tracking Internet users’ activities beginning from a Member’s Website or e-mail. If the Internet user visits or revisits an advertiser’s site directly from such Member, ADSOVO is able to continue to track the Internet user’s activities on the advertiser’s site and reward the Member that referred the Internet user. The Cookies tell ADSOVO nothing about the Internet user personally.

**Cookies are used:**

  * when an advertiser’s banner image or other text is loaded on a Webpage for viewing by an Internet user, and
  * when the banner or other text is clicked by an Internet user.

The function of these Cookies is to provide ADSOVO with information solely for the purpose of paying a Member’s commissions when an Internet user clicks on a link or makes a purchase on an advertiser’s Website.

This Website uses tracking technology to collect visitor behavior data. This data is collected anonymously to be used for marketing and optimization purposes. All visitor data is saved using an anonymous user ID to aggregate a usage profile. Cookies may be used to collect and save this data, but the data remains strictly anonymous. **The data will NOT be used to identify a visitor personally** and are not aggregated with any personal data. The collection and storage of data may be refused at any time with respect to subsequent services.

**Delete ADSOVO cookies on Mozilla Firefox**  
1\. On the menu bar, click on the Firefox menu and select Preferences.   
2\. Select the Privacy panel.  
3\. Set Firefox will: to Use custom settings for history.   
4\. Click” Show Cookies…” The Cookies window will appear.   
5\. In the Search: field, type “adsovo.com” and/or “ad1.adsovo.com”. The cookies that match your search will be displayed.  
6.Select the cookie(s) in the list to remove and click Remove Cookie.  
7\. Close the Cookies window.

**Delete ADSOVO cookies on Safari**  
1\. Select “Preferences” from the top Safari menu.  
2\. Click the “Security” tab.  
3\. Select “Show Cookies”.  
4\. Select “adsovo.com” and/or “ad1.adsovo.com” highlight them and select “Remove”  
5\. Read the confirmation message and click “Remove”.  
6\. Select “Done”  
7\. Close the dialog box.

**Delete cookies in Internet Explorer  8**  
1.Open Internet Explorer by clicking the Start button , and then clicking Internet Explorer.   
2.Click the Safety button, and then click Delete Browsing History.  
3.Select the check box next to Cookies.  
4.Select the Preserve Favorites website data check box if you do not want to delete the cookies associated with websites in your Favorites list.  
5.Click Delete.

### Member-Identifiable Data

ADSOVO collects certain personally identifiable information from persons and entities wishing to join the Network. The collection of this information is a part of normal business practices. Persons and entities wishing to become Members and join the Network are asked to provide personally identifiable data through the sign up and registration process.

Examples of personally identifiable data that may be requested include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, tax ID number, VAT number, etc. All personally identifiable information that ADSOVO collects from potential and actual Members is principally intended for internal administrative needs such as accounting and invoicing.

Periodically ADSOVO may desire to communicate with the Network of Members via e-mail newsletters or other methods to offer marketing information or other communications to assist in business related activities. In such instances ADSOVO will access Members’ personally identifiable information. In the event that a Member wishes not to have personally identifiable information used as described in this paragraph, such Member may elect to opt-out by notifying ADSOVO in writing or electronically at any time.

All personally identifiable data provided by individual Members will be kept in strict confidence by ADSOVO and will be treated with the same level of care that ADSOVO treats its other proprietary information and trade secrets; notwithstanding the foregoing, ADSOVO may in limited instances provide personally identifiable information to a third party to assist ADSOVO in normal and customary operational and statistical matters, or for efficiency purposes in providing administrative services such as billing, delivery and payouts. Any third-party receiving such information will be required to treat it in a confidential and safeguarded manner, in accordance with industry standards and in accordance with the policies stated herein. In the event that a Member wishes not to have personally identifiable information used as described in this paragraph, such Members may elect to opt-out by notifying ADSOVO in writing or electronically at any time.

### Security Precautions

ADSOVO makes every effort to maintain the security of its Network, business operations and any and all data collected. Any data that is stored on ADSOVO’s servers are treated as proprietary and confidential and is not available to the public. ADSOVO has a strict internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees or third parties that have a need to know such information for the purpose of effectively delivering ADSOVO’s products and services; notwithstanding any other provision herein, information may be disclosed:

  * to government agencies or officials or other third parties if ADSOVO believes such disclosure to be required or compelled under applicable law or regulations or legal process;
  * to government agencies or officials upon their request, even if not compelled by a subpoena or other legal process, and without any duty on ADSOVO’s part to independently confirm that such agencies or officials are legally entitled to such disclosure;
  * to a buyer, subcontractor or agent, in the event that ADSOVO sells or transfers ownership, operation or control of any or all of its Networks or engages any subcontractor or agent to operate any Network or provide any service related to any Network.

### Access to Data

ADSOVO allows Members and potential Members who have provided personally identifiable data, access to such data at any reasonable time, in order to ensure that such data is correct, and to make any changes.

### Privacy Policy Statements of Members

ADSOVO encourages all Websites within the Network to create privacy policy statements and provide Internet users with prominently placed access to such statements. Additionally, ADSOVO requests that all Website publishers doing business with ADSOVO disclose any and all information that is being collected from Internet users on their Website, including data gathered from banners and other forms of advertising being served on their Website.

### Spam and E-mail lists

ADSOVO does not intentionally send unsolicited e-mail messages that could be construed as spam; Members’ actions are carefully scrutinized and each Member is expected to adhere to ADSOVO’s anti-spam policy.

### Miscellaneous

Various state and federal regulations may apply to the online collection of personal information from children under the age of 13. ADSOVO is sensitive to the issue of children’s privacy and makes every effort to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. ADSOVO’s Website, products, and services are neither developed for, nor directed at, children.
